RICHARD L. WOOTEN

Brandeburg Development Group, Inc. 1300 Citizens Blvd, Suite 110, Leesburg, FL 34748

Cell (352) 205-3910 Work (352) 435-0500 Fax (352) 435-0501 Richard@brandeburg.com Richwoo@aol.com

CAPABILITIES & QUALIFICATIONS

Executive Experience and Education as support for Real Estate Development Career

Richard Wooten served the Health Care Industry for over 25 years in various senior management roles including Chief Financial Officer, Chief Operating Officer, and Chief Executive Officer. The Businesses ranged from rural stand-alone facilities to Metro area Healthcare systems with net revenues in excess of \$250 million. During the course of his career he had multiple opportunities to finance, acquire, and develop Land, Commercial real estate, Buildings, Businesses, and Health related service lines in excess of \$100 million dollars. His experiences provide a unique foundation for his continuing career in the Real Estate and Development area.

Profile Health Care Administration and Consulting

Market Analysis / Strategic Planning

Financial Analysis / Financing

Business Structure / Joint Venture

Leasing / Property Management

Facility Design

Property Acquisition / Campus Planning

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HEALTHCARE / BUSINESS CONSULTANT

Leesburg, FL

Independent healthcare / business consulting with expertise in physician ventures, financial planning, new product development, and medical commercial real estate feasibility analysis. 2005 - Present

Engagements:

- Physician owned center:
 - > Project financial forecasting for project viability.
 - > Program planning for budgeting of human resources and asset utilization.
 - > Development of implementation action plans.
 - Assisted with venture capital acquisition and analyzed the proposals.
- Business development and marketing strategy for entrepreneurial venture targeting patient mobilization capabilities. Defined market testing underway.
- Proforma analysis for commercial property business project viability.
- Business planning for lease vs. owned Urgent Care Center

PRESIDENT / CEO

Leesburg Regional Medical Center, Inc., Leesburg, FL

Responsible for all operation aspects of the day to day leadership and management functions of the \$250 million, 489 bed, multi-facility healthcare system including planning and initiation of facilities and services for north central Florida region. The facilities include: Leesburg Regional Medical Center (LRMC), The Villages Regional Hospital (TVRH), Central Florida Healthcare Development Corporation (parent company), and other subsidiary companies. Additionally responsible to uphold and promote the corporate mission and philosophies, provide the resources to achieve its vision and operate within the stated guiding principles. 1998 - 2005

Quorum Health Resources, Inc.

(Formerly HCA Management Company)

Early assignments were with the Management Company which was acquired to become Quorum. They are a contract management company providing Executive staff to hospitals. 1983 - 1998

ADMINISTRATOR/CEO

Jackson Hospital

Marianna, FL

Responsible for the ongoing operations of this 107 bed acute care hospital including medical staff, board of trustees, employees, auxiliary, and community well-being.

Leesburg Regional Medical Center

Leesburg, FL

Two leadership positions held as a member of the Quorum team. (1986 - 1995)

VICE PRESIDENT

Responsible for departmental direction and coordination of the 414 bed med/surg/SNF organization to include Laboratory, Diagnostic Imaging, Information Systems, Pharmacy, Biomed Engineering, Plant Maintenance, Human Resources, Cardio Pulmonary, Construction, Medical Records, Environmental Services, Admitting, Security, Food and Nutrition, and Materiels Management. (1993 - 1995)

CONTROLLER

Responsibilities included daily hospital operations of the financial and business office areas, including Information Systems, General Accounting, Accounts Payable, Payroll, Admitting, and Materiels Management. Considerable involvement with Medical Staff, Long Range Strategic Planning, Cash Management, Annual Budget, Annual Management Action Plan, and financial feasibility studies. (1986 - 1993)

CONTROLLER

South Lake Memorial Hospital

Clermont, FL (1983 - 1986 HCA Management Company)

Responsible for all financial operations of the 68 bed acute care facility including departmental direction and coordination for Accounting, Business Office, Materiels Management and Medical Records.

ASSISTANT CONTROLLER

Hospital Corporation of America

Marion Community Hospital, Ocala, FL

Responsible for Accounting, Accounts Payable, Data Processing, and Payroll Departments at the 190-bed facility. 1980 – 1983

- Assisted HCA Internal Audit Department with External Engagements.
- Assisted HCA Management Company as Interim Controller at James Archer Smith Hospital in Homestead, Florida from February through March of 1983.

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration 1993

Nova University, Davie, FL

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration - Finance 1980

University of Florida, Gainesville, FL

Associate of Arts 1978

Central Florida Community College, Ocala, FL

PROFESSIONAL AND CIVIC AFFILIATIONS

American College of Healthcare Executives, Member

Florida Hospital Association: Legislative Committee - 1998

Healthcare Financial Management Association

Leadership Lake County - Class of 1995

Chamber of Commerce, Board of Directors Tri-County 1996

Rotary International, 1995 - 1997

Habilitative Services, Board of Directors 1996-1997

Panhandle Area Health Network, Board of Directors 1995-1997

Lake Sumter United Way, Board of Directors

Leesburg Chamber of Commerce, Board of Directors 1998-2004

Lake County Comprehensive Health Planning Council, Board of Directors 1998-2005

Lake County Schools Superintendent's Advisory Committee

Community Medical Care Clinic, Board of Directors 2002-2005

Voluntary Hospital of America South East (VHA/SE) Board of Directors 1999-2005

HPA Group Purchasing Initiative, Board of Directors 2003-2005

The Villages Regional Hospital, Board of Directors 2001-2005

Lake County Republican Executive Committee 2004-2005

Community Development Corporation, Board of Directors 1998 -2005

REAL ESTATE BACKGROUND

Licensed as Real Estate Associate in October of 2005. License Number SL3143284 and began working with Brandeburg Development Group, Inc., John Brandeburg Broker-Owner.

PERSONAL BACKGROUND

Married to Sharon Wooten with four children, Kimberly 19, Jennifer 17, Matthew 15, and Lauren 13. Have resided in Lake County, Florida since 1998.